All right. Now on to the best part.
现在进入最精彩的环节
We're going to make the app look really good now.
我们将使该应用看起来非常美观
In every developer's workflow it's important to set aside time for
在所有开发者的工作流程中 一定要预留一些时间
some visual polish before launching the app to your user.
来改善应用外观 然后再向用户发布应用
So often, when you're building a feature, you're less worried about how
通常 当你构建某个功能的时候 你不太注意
everything looks and you just care that it actually functions as you expect.
所有内容的外观 只关心是否能像预期的那样正常运转
So in the visual polish stage, you have time to take extra care on how
在外观改善阶段 你将有时间更加仔细地观察
everything looks making sure things line up and are consistent for users.
所有外观 确保内容按序排列 并且对用户来说是稳定的
So now it's time to show great care for your app.
现在来好好关心下你的应用外观吧
So our designer gave us these red lines which have specific details for color,
设计师给出了这些红色标示 详细地注明了颜色
font size, and spacing.
字体大小和间隔
And these red lines are how the designer communicates to us precisely how our app
设计师正是通过这些红色标示告诉我们应用的外观
should look visually.
具体应该是怎样的
So for every detail that they provide,
对于他们提供的每个细节
be sure to implement that into your app code.
确保实施到你的应用代码里
So if the red lines say 16 DP spacing from the left, then go ahead and
如果红色标示注明距离左侧 16dp
modify your layout to have that 16 DP of spacing.
那么请修改你的布局 并实现该 16dp 的间隔
The font color and font size may also need to change.
字体颜色和字体大小可能也需要修改
So note that each category of words should have a different
注意 每个单词类别应该具有不同的
background color.
背景颜色
So orange for numbers, green for family, purple for colors, and blue for phrases.
Numbers 是橘色 Family 是绿色 Colors 是紫色 Phrases 是蓝色
So it's going to take us multiple quizzes to finish implementing all those
要实施所有这些红色标示的细节 我们需要完成好几道
red lines.
测试题
So in this quiz assume that orange is fine as the background color for
在这道测试题中 假设所有 Activity 都可以具有橘色
all the activities.
背景颜色
We'll correct it so
我们将稍后修改背景颜色
that each activity has a corresponding correct color later on.
使每个 Activity 都具有对应的正确颜色
So in a way, orange is our placeholder color until we can hook up the correct
某种程度上 在我们为应用实现正确的背景颜色逻辑前
logic in our app.
橘色就是我们的占位符颜色
So to help you out, you may want to check out a feature on Android devices
为了帮助你完成操作 请使用 Android 设备上
specifically for developers called show layout bounds.
针对开发者的某项功能 叫做 Show layout bounds
And you can turn it on under settings,
你可以依次转到“设置 (Settings)” “开发者选项 (Developer options)”
developer options, and then scroll down to show layout bounds.
然后向下滚动 找到“显示布局边界 (Show layout bounds)”开启该功能
When you turn the switch, you'll see all the bounds on the screen.
打开开关后 你将在屏幕上看到所有的边界
So if we go back to Miwok app, we can see where all the views are.
回到 Miwok 应用 我们可以看到所有视图位于何处
So turning on this feature temporarily may help you figure out how to fix your
暂时开启此功能可以帮助你知道如何修改布局
layouts, but note it's not required.
但并非必须这么做
All right, so have fun implementing those red lines.
希望你能开心地实施这些红色指示的细节
We've included some hints below the quiz if you need some help.
我们在测试题下提供了一些提示 帮助你完成操作
And go ahead and check this box once you're done.
完成后 请选中该方框